<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
  <title>Massages</title>
  <description>All types of massage at a glance</description>
  <img src="img/small/ontspanning.jpg" alt="massage"/>
  <quote>To keep the body in good health
  is a duty&#x2026;<br/> otherwise we shall not
  be able to keep our mind strong<br/>
  and clear</quote>
  <quotee>Buddha</quotee>
  <story>
    <h1>Massages</h1>
    <h2>What is classic relaxation massage?</h2>

    <p>Take a moment for yourself and enjoy a classic relaxation massage. A massage will make you aware of and help to relieve tension in your body. This type of massage is commonly referred to as a normal massage, relaxation massage or therapeutic massage.</p>

    <p>This form of massage is used to overcome physical (or psychological) symptoms of tension and pain (stress, neck aches, backaches, and muscular pain), but also helps to maintain balance and a healthy body.</p>

    <p>The therapist applies techniques such as kneading and massage strokes to stimulate the blood circulation of the skin, connective tissue and muscular tissue. This helps to remove toxins from the body faster, and allows nutrients to penetrate deep in the tissue.</p>

    <p>Massage therapy has a relaxing effect on both the body and mind. If desired, you may request a firmer massage. This is commonly also referred to as an active massage.</p>



    <h2 id="sportmassages">What is Sports massage?</h2>

    <p><div class="fancybox-wrapper"><a class="fancybox" href="/img/sport.jpg"><img class="ie-img-shadow" src="/img/small/sport.jpg" alt="sports massage"></img><br/>+ enlarge</a></div>
    Sports massage is a form of massage that is used to prevent injury and/or muscular pain, and to help the body recover after physical activity.</p>

    <p>The massage therapist applies hand techniques to specific parts of the body. These are aimed at helping to improve or maintain the sports practitioner’s physical condition, and/or to relieve any negative effects such as injuries.</p>

    <p>This form of massage helps to improve the body’s blood circulation and metabolism. The therapist stimulates the muscles, which helps to remove toxins (moisture) from the body. The therapist first applies pressure and then allows the muscle to relax. This has a positive effect on the body’s muscle tension.</p>

    <p>This form of massage has a positive effect on the body. It leads to shorter recovery periods, helps you to breathe more deeply, helps induce sleep and improves your mood.</p>

    <h2 id="stoelmassages">What is a chair massage?</h2>
    <p><div class="fancybox-wrapper"><a class="fancybox" href="/img/stoelmassage.jpg"><img class="ie-img-shadow"  src="/img/small/stoelmassage.jpg" alt="chair massage"></img><br/>+ enlarge</a></div>The phenomenon known as ‘chair massage’ originated in the United States and is widely applied in companies and government institutions. This Japanese pressure point massage is used to help prevent stress and RSI, and to improve your physical and mental condition. This is achieved via a twenty-minute massage whereby the person’s neck, shoulders, back, arms and hands are treated. The treatment helps to relax muscles and makes them supple, resulting in a better immune system and blood circulation.</p>

    <p>The massage is performed on a special massage chair. It was specifically designed to allow you to relax, and enables the therapist to massage your back, neck, arms and hands, and to relieve aches or pains. Anyone can enjoy a chair massage. You will remain fully clothed during treatment, and can quickly return to your daily activities afterwards.</p>

    <h2 id="hotstone">What is a hot stone massage?</h2>
    <p><div class="fancybox-wrapper"><a class="fancybox" href="/img/hotstone.jpg"><img class="ie-img-shadow" id="hotstone" src="/img/small/hotstone.jpg" alt="hotstone"></img><br/>+ groter</a></div>Hot stone massage is a form of massage whereby heated stones are placed on the body. Volcanic basalt stones have an ‘earthing’ effect and give energy. This helps to improve blood circulation, removes toxins from the body and even helps to cleanse organs.</p>

    <p>The heat that is generated by the stones has a relaxing and therapeutic effect on the body’s muscles, bones and nerves. This causes energy to flow throughout the body. During treatment,  one or more stones will be removed and this area of the body is then rubbed with oil and massaged with the hot stones.</p>

    <p>Hot stone massage helps to relieve tension, gives you a feeling of tranquillity and helps you to restore balance.</p>

    <p>Hot stone massage treatment is only available as a 60-minute session.</p>
  </story>
</page>
