<?xml version="1.0"?>
<page>
  <title>Wha am I?</title>
  <description>A brief explanation about myself</description>
  <img src="img/robert_davinci_small.jpg" alt="Robert in the dunes"/>
  <quote>I started my practice because I have an own vision</quote>
  <story>
    <h1>Who am I?</h1>
    <p>My name is Robert Geijp (born 2 February 1978 in Leidschendam). After obtaining a degree in sports massage therapy I started a massage &amp; magnetism practice. I subsequently took a course in chair massage therapy. I also currently work as a sports masseur at healthclub Fittness2Gether in Voorburg.</p>

    <ul>
      <li><a href="http://www.nespg.nl/"><acronym title="Nederlandse Examenstichting in de Sport- &amp; Perimedische Gezondheidszorg">NESPG</acronym></a> Qualified (sports) masseur (educational institute: Eerste NVVS in Rotterdam, <a href="http://www.eerste-nvvs.nl">www.eerste-nvvs.nl</a>)</li>
      <li>Certified chair masseur (educational institute: Massage in Beweging in Alphen a/d Rijn, <a href="http://www.massageinbeweging.nl">www.massageinbeweging.nl</a>).</li>
    </ul>

    <p class="educational-logo"><a href="http://www.nespg.nl/"><img id="NESPG_logo" title="Nederlandse Examenstichting in de Sport- &amp; Perimedische Gezondheidszorg" alt="NESPG logo" src="http://www.nespg.nl/images/nespg.jpg"></img></a>
    <a href="http://www.bms-belangenvereniging.nl/"><img src="http://www.bms-belangenvereniging.nl/logo/009428.gif" width="88" height="68" border="0" alt="Lid van de Belangenvereniging voor Beroepsbeoefenaars in de Massage- en Sportverzorgingbranche" /></a></p>

    <h2>Own vision</h2>
    <p>I want to contribute to helping people regain and/or maintain balance in their lives. By enabling them to calm down and relax, and thereby adding to the quality of their life. I aim to achieve this by applying my senses, and using my hands and heart. This is what I love doing most.</p>

    <p>In today’s society everything needs to be done fast. As a result, people tend to lose their balance. This can lead to a loss of well-being.</p>

    <p>We often do not take enough time to really enjoy ourselves and to focus on the things that we love to do, as well as other important aspects such as children who are growing up.</p>

    <p>In order to maintain balance, I believe it is essential to reflect on such matters and to take time for yourself. By going through an unpleasant situation in my personal life, I learned just how important it is to maintain balance. And how your own behaviour effects others.</p>
  </story>
</page>
